Siyuan (Kelvin) Hu

0

+86 13916324695

linkedin.com/in/siyuanhu



kelvin.hu.siyuan@gmail.com

E?

kelvinuknowhu.github.io

Enthusiastic Software Engineer with expertise in Web Development and Data Visualization. Offering 1+ years of experience in full software development lifecycle. Quickly learn and master new technologies and enjoy working in both team and self-directed settings.



Education

•

Master of Engineering: Computer Science

Cornell University - Ithaca, NY

2013-08 - 2017-05

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

New York University Shanghai - Shanghai, China



Work History

2019-11 - 2020-03

2017-08 - 2018-12

Blockchain Developer

Dipole Tech, Shanghai, China

Implemented Ethereum smart contracts using Solidity to provide data access and integrated a React-based content management system with Ethereum smart contracts using Web3 to read and write electric meter data.

2019-03 - 2019-11

Software Engineer I

Uber Advanced Technologies Group, Pittsburgh, PA

Worked under the AVMaps Applications team and focused on building geospatial web tools that enable geo-specialists to produce high-definition maps for self-driving cars. Used React/Redux as the frontend architecture, DeckGL for graphics rendering, and NebulaGL for geometric editing. Other development tools include Jest and Apache Cassandra.

2018-05 - 2018-08

Software Engineer Intern

Uber Advanced Technologies Group, Pittsburgh, PA

Designed and implemented map production web tools for geo-specialists, such as the street-level panorama panel using camera images taken by the in-vehicle cameras and the traffic light labeling tool to collect data for triangulation. Used development tools such as React, MySQL and Jest on regular basis.

2017-01 - 2017-04

Front End Developer Intern

Energo Labs, Shanghai, China

Developed a management portal using React for a distributed peer-to-peer energy exchange platform to monitor electric meter data, manage user data, and visualize internal business data.



Skills

Front End Development: HTML5/CSS3/React/Redux/Webpack/Sass/WebGL2

Back End Development: Node.js/Express/MySQL **Data Science:** D3/Numpy/Pandas/PyTorch/Keras **Programming Languages:** JavaScript/Python/Java